¬ Generated by BinEditor v3.0
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_PENALTY_DESCR}The Knight Sigmar has decided to donate a small amount of money to your cause.
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}You cannot help the Knight Sigmar so his donation will be modest.
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_REWARD_DESCR}You have received a donation from Knight Sigmar
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The more Knight Sigmar wins, the bigger your reward will be.
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_SOURCE}Knight Sigmar
{ASSASSINS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Assassins' Guild
{COUNCIL_MISSION_SOURCE}Council of Nobles
{EXPLORERS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Explorers' Guild
{FACTION_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}This faction thinks less of you.
{FACTION_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}You will disappoint this faction.
{FACTION_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}You have genuinely improved your relations with this faction.
{FACTION_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}You will improve your relations with this faction.
{HUGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen of Chaos has improved enormously.
{HUGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen of Chaos will improve enormously. 
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen of Chaos has suffered enormously.
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen of Chaos will suffer enormously. 
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen of Chaos has improved significantly.
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen of Chaos will improve significantly.
{MAJOR_EXPLORERS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Explorers' Guild is very disappointed in you.
{MAJOR_EXPLORERS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Explorers' Guild will be very disappointed in you.
{MAJOR_EXPLORERS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Explorers' Guild is very happy with you.
{MAJOR_EXPLORERS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Explorers' Guild will be very happy with you
{MASONS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Masons' Guild
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen has suffered significantly.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen will suffer significantly.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen has improved.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen will improve. 
{MERCHANTS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Merchants' Guild
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild will be not impressed with your efforts.
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild appreciates your efforts.
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild is far from impressed with your efforts.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}Everchosen' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Everchosen' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}Everchosen' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Everchosen' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is impressed with you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be impressed with you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is thankful to you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be thankful to you.
{ORDER_COUNCIL_MISSION_SOURCE}Tip about the Order.
{PLACE_OF_WORSHIP_REWARD_DESCR}The Masons' Guild has built you a place of worship.
{PLACE_OF_WORSHIP_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Masons' Guild have offered to construct place of worship for you.
{POPE_MISSION_SOURCE}Everchosen
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen is not as high as it once was.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen will not be as high as it once was.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen has improved slightly.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Everchosen will improve slightly.
{VNV_ADORED_BY_POPE_DESCR}The Everchosen considers your leader one of his closest allies.
{VNV_ADORED_BY_POPE_PRE_DESCR}Your leader will become one of the Everchosen's closest allies. 
{VNV_POPES_ENFORCER_DESCR}Your leader is the steel gauntlet of the Everchosen's will.
{VNV_POPES_ENFORCER_PRE_DESCR}Your leader will become the steel gauntlet of the Everchosen's will.
{adventure_crusader_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This Order allied itself with Kislev.
{adventure_crusader_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Knight Everchosen is dead - a great shame for all who followed him.
{adventure_crusader_FAILURE}You did not help enough. The Everchosen returned home and left some change left.
{adventure_crusader_PROPOSAL}Help the newly arrived Knight Everchosen in fulfilling his sacred vows and he will leave a substantial donation.
{adventure_crusader_SUCCESS}Knights of Everchosen were successful. The left generous donations in gratitude for the help and returned home.
{adventure_crusader_TITLE}Assist the Everchosen
{annex_settlement_EXPIRY_DEATH}The faction you were to treaty with has been vanquished. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to them. 
{annex_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another faction has taken this settlement. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to this faction.
{annex_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to convince our rivals to hand over this settlement; the Council is greatly disappointed at this turn of events.
{annex_settlement_PROPOSAL}By rights, this settlement should be under our authority. It is a mockery for it to be held by our rivals. The Council suggests you send a diplomat and attempt to have them to hand it over. You may be able to offer them a settlement that is less valuable to us in exchange.
{annex_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully convinced this faction to hand over land that is rightfully ours; the Council is much impressed by your obvious authority.
{annex_settlement_TITLE}Annex Settlement
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This man has become our ally; it is no longer necessary to remove him.
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_DEATH}Your target has died; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_HIDING}Your target has gone into hiding; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_captain_FAILURE}You have failed to assassinate this individual; the Council assumes this must be part of your great plan.
{assassinate_captain_PROPOSAL}This miscreant's demise would please a great many people, not to mention make smoother our path to success. The Council suggests you send an assassin to hasten this man's journey into the next world. 
{assassinate_captain_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully assassinated this individual; the Council is impressed by your ruthlessness.
{assassinate_captain_TITLE}Assassination Mission
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_DEATH}As this man has died, the Everchosen has no need for you to 'deal' with him.
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}You have been excommunicated, the Everchosen no longer trusts you with this important duty.
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_HIDING}This man cannot be found, the Everchosen has no need for you to 'deal' with him.
{assassinate_cardinal_FAILURE}The Everchosen is disquieted by your failure to 'deal' with this man.
{assassinate_cardinal_PROPOSAL}This man's profanity and disrespect has deeply distressed the Everchosen. He assures you that the Gods will smile upon you if you can deal with this delicate matter (kill him!).
{assassinate_cardinal_SUCCESS}You have done the Everchosen a great favour, and much pleased the Everchosen by successfully assassinating this Cardinal.
{assassinate_cardinal_TITLE}Assassinate Everchosen 
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This man has become our ally; it is no longer necessary to remove him.
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_DEATH}Your target has died; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_HIDING}Your target has gone into hiding; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_general_FAILURE}You have failed to assassinate this individual; the Council assumes this must be part of your great plan.
{assassinate_general_PROPOSAL}This miscreant's demise would please a great many people, not to mention make smoother our path to success. The Council suggests you send an assassin to hasten this man's journey into the next world. 
{assassinate_general_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully assassinated this individual; the Council is impressed by your ruthlessness.
{assassinate_general_TITLE}Assassination Mission
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Everchosen has no need for you to assassinate this person, as they have perished.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Everchosen does not trust the likes of you to uphold the Word of Sigmar. You are no longer charged with the assassination of this person.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_HIDING}The Everchosen has no need for you to assassinate this person, as they cannot be found.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Everchosen by failing to assassinate this blasphemer as asked.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_PROPOSAL}This blasphemer is a stain on the world and the Everchosen wishes you to cleanse it. Assassinate this person immediately!
{assassinate_witch_heretic_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully assassinating this blasphemer, and thus making the world more pleasing to His eye.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_TITLE}Assassinate the heretic
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{blockade_distant_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{blockade_distant_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 1 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{blockade_distant_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{blockade_distant_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_FAILURE}You have let down the Everchosen and the Gods by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_heretic_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to both punish these heretics and stop their unholy rot from spreading to the faithful.
{blockade_heretic_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen and the gods by successfully blockading this port.
{blockade_heretic_TITLE}Blockade Port
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has come to the fold, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_FAILURE}You have let down the Everchosen and the gods by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_islam_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to weaken these enemies of the Gods.
{blockade_islam_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen and the Gods by successfully blockading this port.
{blockade_islam_TITLE}Blockade Port
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{blockade_moderate_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{blockade_moderate_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 2 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{blockade_moderate_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{blockade_moderate_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has come to the fold, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_FAILURE}You have let down the Everchosen and the Gods by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_pagan_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to both punish these heathens and stop their unholy rot from spreading to the faithful.
{blockade_pagan_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen of Chaos and Sigmar by successfully blockading this port.
{blockade_pagan_TITLE}Blockade Port
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_DEATH}As this faction has perished, you are no longer required to break your alliance with them.
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer required to break your alliance with this faction.
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer required to break your alliance with them.
{break_alliance_FAILURE}The Everchosen can only wonder what went wrong; you have disappointed the him by failing to break your alliance with this faction. 
{break_alliance_PROPOSAL}In uncertain times like these, it is important to know who one's true allies are. The Everchosen demands you break your alliance with this profane and heretical faction to prove your loyalty.
{break_alliance_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen and proven your loyalty by successfully breaking your alliance with this faction.
{break_alliance_TITLE}Break Alliance
{castle_chapel_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Everchosen cares naught what you build in this castle.
{castle_chapel_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this castle, you are no longer charged with building a daemon alter there.
{castle_chapel_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by failing to build a daemon alter in this castle, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Gods in this castle.
{castle_chapel_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Everchosen's attention that this castle is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a daemon alter in this castle.
{castle_chapel_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully building an alter in this castle, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Gods in this castle.
{castle_chapel_TITLE}Build a Daemon Alter
{castle_small_chapel_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Everchosen cares naught what you build in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this castle, you are no longer charged with building an alter there.
{castle_small_chapel_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by failing to build a alter in this castle, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Gods in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Everchosen's attention that this castle is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a alter to the gods in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully building an alter in this castle, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Gods in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_TITLE}Build a Small Chapel
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Everchosen is no longer concerned about the fate of this faction as it has been eliminated.
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless and ignoble faction has been excommunicated, the Chaos Gods no longer expects such as you to listen to the request of the Everchosen of Chaos.
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_TARGET_EXCOMMUNICATED}As this faction has been excommunicated, it matters little how much of their faithless blood you spill. You are no longer charged with ceasing hostilities with this faction.
{cease_hostilities_FAILURE}You have greatly saddened the Everchosen by failing to cease hostilities with your fellow chaos, and continuing to shed the blood of your brother.
{cease_hostilities_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen demands that you stop shedding the blood of your fellow Chaos. Cease hostilities against this faction immediately and do not carry out hostile acts for the duration of this mission.
{cease_hostilities_SUCCESS}You have greatly pleased the Everchosen by refraining from hostile actions against your fellow chaos. He only hopes this newfound peace will last.
{cease_hostilities_TITLE}Cease Hostilities
{city_abbey_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Everchosen cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_abbey_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building an Abadía there.
{city_abbey_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by failing to build an Abadía in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Gods in this city.
{city_abbey_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Everchosen's attention that this settlement is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build an Abadía in this settlement.
{city_abbey_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully building an Abadía in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_abbey_TITLE}Build a Daemon Alter
{city_cathedral_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Everchosen cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_cathedral_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a Cathedral there.
{city_cathedral_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by failing to build a daemon alter in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of the gods in this city.
{city_cathedral_PROPOSAL}It has come to His Holiness's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. The Everchosen wishes you to build a daemon alter in this city.
{city_cathedral_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully building a daemon alter in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of the gods in this city.
{city_cathedral_TITLE}Daemon Alter
{city_huge_cathedral_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Everchosen cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a daemon alter there.
{city_huge_cathedral_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen of Chaos by failing to build a daemon alter in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Everchosen of Chaos's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a daemon alter in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen of Chaos by successfully building a Huge Cathedral in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_TITLE}Build a Daemon Alter
{city_small_church_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Everchosen cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_small_church_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a Daemon Alter there.
{city_small_church_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by failing to build a Daemon Alter in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Gods in this city.
{city_small_church_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Everchosen's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a Daemon Alter in this city.
{city_small_church_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully building a Daemon Alter in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Gods in this city.
{city_small_church_TITLE}Build a Daemon Alter
{convert_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your ungodly faction has been excommunicated. One cannot expect a nest of vipers to bring forward the lambs. You are no longer charged with converting the people to the 'one true faith. 
{convert_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by failing to convert sufficient people in this settlement.
{convert_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen sees that the unbelievers in this settlement are clouding the judgement of the righteous. Send a priest to convert at least %d %% of the population to Chaos.
{convert_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully spreading the word and converting more believers in this settlement.
{convert_TITLE}Spread the Word of the Gods
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{council_blockade_port_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{council_blockade_port_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 3 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{council_blockade_port_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{council_blockade_port_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_GENERAL_DEATH}Alas this marriage can never be, the general has died, and nearly left our Princess a widow.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_DEATH}Alas, the poor Princess has died; we must call the marriage off.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_RETIRED}Our Princess is now too old to marry; her time would be better spent on more solitary and contemplative pursuits. The marriage is off.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_TARGET_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, and this lord is twice such, he has married another. The marriage to our Princess is off.
{council_marry_princess_FAILURE}You have not arranged the marriage this Council recommended. The Council bows to your greater judgement in these matters.
{council_marry_princess_FAILURE_PRINCESS_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, it seems our Princess has married another, the original marriage is off.
{council_marry_princess_PROPOSAL}Lord %S has been beguiled by the lovely Princess %S. He is willing to pay a handsome dowry for her hand in marriage. The Council recommends you arrange this marriage as soon as possible.
{council_marry_princess_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully arranged the marriage we recommended. This union is sure to bear fruit in time.
{council_marry_princess_TITLE}A Proposal for the Princess's Hand
{council_take_rebel_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this Rebel settlement. You are no longer required to take it.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_FAILURE}It appears you have decided against this Council's advice by not taking this Rebel settlement, the Council can only assume this is yet another sudden turn in your labyrinth-like plan.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_PROPOSAL}Our great nation appears weak to tolerate such insolence from these rebels. The Council recommends you capture this rebel settlement and assert your authority.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this Rebel settlement and displayed our strength to all.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_TITLE}Take Rebel Settlement
{council_take_settlement_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to take it.
{council_take_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this settlement.
{council_take_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to take this settlement; perhaps you felt it was not the right time to expand our borders?
{council_take_settlement_PROPOSAL}It is time to further our great empire by extending our borders. The Council suggests you take this settlement for the glory of the nation.
{council_take_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this settlement, and extended our Empire.
{council_take_settlement_TITLE}Take Settlement
{crusade_active_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen has called for a Chaos Incursion to this settlement. It is time for slaughter and bloodshed.
{crusade_active_TARGET_PROPOSAL}It is a nightmarish day for your people that inhabit this settlement, for the Everchosen has called a Chaos Incursion against it! The seemingly endless armies of Chaos will soon be marching to lay siege to the walls... The end times are near!
{crusade_active_TITLE}A Chaos Incursion
{gift_from_council_PROPOSAL}The Council are greatly impressed by your leadership and would like you to accept this humble offering as a token of past and future endeavours.
{gift_from_council_TITLE}A Gift from the Council
{gift_from_pope_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen has noticed your faithful dedication to the Chaos Gods and is pleased to grant you this gift.
{gift_from_pope_TITLE}A Gift from the Everchosen
{give_ancillary_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by coveting this relic and thus failing to hand it over to him.
{give_ancillary_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen has heard of your retrieval of this wondrous unholy relic and sends his congratulations. You must hand over this relic so that it may reside with him, as is proper.
{give_ancillary_SUCCESS}The Everchosen sends you his gratitude for the rightful return of this unholy relic to the the Gods.
{give_ancillary_TITLE}Give Relic to the Everchosen
{give_cash_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen with your selfishness, by failing to "donate" sufficient gold to him.
{give_cash_PROPOSAL}Nurgle favours he who is generous. Make a "donation" of at least %d florins to the the Everchosen. 
{give_cash_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen with your generous "donation". Blessed is he who gives.
{give_cash_TITLE}Give a "donation" to the Everchosen
{guild_acquisition_EXPIRY_DEATH}It appears this merchant has perished; we no longer need to remove him.
{guild_acquisition_EXPIRY_HIDING}It appears this merchant has gone into hiding; we no longer need to remove him. 
{guild_acquisition_FAILURE}You have failed to complete the desired acquisition; the Guild is disappointed with this outcome. 
{guild_acquisition_PROPOSAL}There is lucrative trade to be had here, but first we must deal with the opposition. The Guild recommends you send your merchant to make an acquisition of this merchants' trade. 
{guild_acquisition_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully made the acquisition; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_acquisition_TITLE}Mercantile Acquisition
{guild_build_PROPOSAL}In recognition of your past aid and support to the Mason's Guild, the masons will build a place of worship in your honour, so that the faithful may gather.
{guild_build_TITLE}A Gift from the Mason's Guild
{guild_recruit_agent_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train an assassin there.
{guild_recruit_agent_FAILURE}You have failed to train an assassin; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_agent_PROPOSAL}Sometimes a single drop of poison or one knife in the dark can achieve what an entire army cannot. The Guild requests that you train an assassin in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_agent_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained an assassin, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_agent_TITLE}Train Assassin
{guild_recruit_merchant_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are sufficient merchants for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a merchant.
{guild_recruit_merchant_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Merchant there.
{guild_recruit_merchant_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Merchant; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_merchant_PROPOSAL}Three things are required to make war and conquest; gold, gold and more gold. The Guild requests that you train a Merchant in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_merchant_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Merchant, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_merchant_TITLE}Train Merchant
{guild_recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are enough of Sigmar's soldiers for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a priest. 
{guild_recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Priest there.
{guild_recruit_priest_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Priest; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_priest_PROPOSAL}The Holy word requires another soldier of faith. The Guild requests that you train a Priest in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_priest_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Priest, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_priest_TITLE}Train Priest
{guild_recruit_spy_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Spy there.
{guild_recruit_spy_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Spy; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_spy_PROPOSAL}Sometimes a little bit of information is worth a dozen armies. The Guild requests that you train a Spy in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_spy_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Spy, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_spy_TITLE}Train Spy
{guild_take_settlement_EXPIRY_ALLIED}An alliance has been forged with this settlement, the Guild no longer requires you to take it.
{guild_take_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this settlement, the Guild no longer requires you to take it.
{guild_take_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to take this settlement; the Guild is disappointed with this lack of progress.
{guild_take_settlement_PROPOSAL}The Guild's interests would be better looked after if this settlement were to become part of your empire. The Guild requests that you take this settlement.
{guild_take_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this settlement; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_take_settlement_TITLE}Take Settlement
{guild_trade_agreement_EXPIRY_DEATH}This faction has been vanquished; a trade agreement with them is no longer possible.
{guild_trade_agreement_EXPIRY_WAR}These fools have chosen war with us rather than peaceful trade. So be it, a trade agreement with them is no longer possible. 
{guild_trade_agreement_FAILURE}You have not obtained a trade agreement with this faction; the Guild is disappointed with this outcome.
{guild_trade_agreement_PROPOSAL}We are losing lucrative trade opportunities, as we currently have no trade Agreement with this faction. The Guild would like you to obtain a trade agreement with these people.
{guild_trade_agreement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully obtained a Trade Agreement with this faction; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_trade_agreement_TITLE}Obtain Trade Agreement
{jihad_active_PROPOSAL}An army is moving on this settlement to clean away the hated enemy. It is time to dispense rightful anger upon these fools.
{jihad_active_TARGET_PROPOSAL}A great Shaman has called for warriors to take up arms against your people and descend upon this settlement! The willingness of the soldiers' to die for such a cause make this one of the most terrifying perils the people of this place will ever face... Ensure they are prepared.
{jihad_active_TITLE}A Waaagh!
{join_crusade_CHARACTER_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen has requested that %S demonstrate his faith and personally join the Chaos Incursion.
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_DEATH}Your General has died. As a result, you can no longer join the Chaos Incursion.
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You have no place amongst the worthy; you can no longer join the Chaos Incursion.
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_FINISHED}the Chaos Incursion has ended; you can no longer join. 
{join_crusade_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by not meeting your obligations to the Gods and failing to join the Chaos Incursion.
{join_crusade_HEIR_TITLE}Your Heir must join the Chaos Incursion.
{join_crusade_LEADER_TITLE}Your Leader must join the Chaos Incursion.
{join_crusade_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen has called a Chaos Incursion, and he has sent the call to arms to all devoted the Gods. You must create a Crusading army within the time limit to take part.
{join_crusade_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen and proven your faith by successfully joining the Chaos Incursion. 
{join_crusade_TITLE}Join the Chaos Incursion
{kill_crusader_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This Knight is now our new ally. He should be left untouched.
{kill_crusader_EXPIRY_DEATH}Your incompetence is clearly visible. You have not eliminated this man.
{kill_crusader_EXPIRY_HIDING}It is not possible to locate this man. He went into hiding like a coward. The mission is over.
{kill_crusader_FAILURE}Your incompetence is clearly visible. You have not eliminated this man.
{kill_crusader_PROPOSAL}This character is a direct threat to our nation. He must be eliminated at all costs.
{kill_crusader_SUCCESS}You are succesful at helping this man ending his poor life.
{kill_crusader_TITLE}Kill the Knight Everchosen
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_FAILURE}You have let down the Everchosen and the Gods by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{papal_blockade_port_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen only wishes that this man be returned to the fold. Perhaps cutting his income will make him see the light. Use your fleet to blockade this port for at least 3 turns.
{papal_blockade_port_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen and the gods by successfully blockading this port.
{papal_blockade_port_TITLE}Blockade Port
{papal_build_church_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Everchosen cares naught what you build in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, you are no longer charged with building a alter there.
{papal_build_church_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen of Chaos by failing to build a alter in this settlement, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Gods in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Everchosen's attention that this settlement is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build an alter in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully building a church in this settlement, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Gods in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_TITLE}Build an alter
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your worthless faction has been excommunicated, a priest from such a flock would be at best worthless. You are no longer charged with recruiting a priest.
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are enough of Sigmar's servants for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a priest. 
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LOST}You have lost this settlement, you are no longer charged with recruiting a priest.
{recruit_priest_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by failing to recruit a priest, and thus hampering his unholy work.
{recruit_priest_PROPOSAL}The dwindling number of Chaos in this settlement reflects poorly on the the Gods. Recruit a priest in this settlement to convert more people.
{recruit_priest_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Everchosen by successfully recruiting a priest, and thus creating yet another vessel for the Gods Word.
{recruit_priest_TITLE}Recruit a Priest
{regicide_EXPIRY_DEATH}My 'noble' father has perished; you are no longer required to 'intervene'.
{regicide_EXPIRY_HIDING}My father has gone to ground like the mole he is, you are no longer required to 'intervene'. 
{regicide_EXPIRY_SOURCE_DEATH}Наследник трона отошел в мир иной, и вам более не нужно исполнять его жестокие приказы. Но неужели все ваши труды окажутся напрасными? В конце концов, нет ничего зазорного в устранении очередного соперника...
{regicide_FAILURE}You have failed to deal with my wretched father as I requested, I will not forget this.
{regicide_PROPOSAL}My father is naught but a simpering fool. If left to rule he will bring only ruin to what should be my empire. Kill him so that I may lead my empire to greatness, and our empires will rule the world side by side as brothers. I am willing to generously 'recompense' you for your troubles.
{regicide_SUCCESS}You have my endless gratitude; you have done both my people and myself a great favour. Your deed may go unsung but it will not go unrewarded, nor forgotten.
{regicide_TITLE}Regicide
{reinforce_region_EXPIRY_LOST}It is too late, the settlement is lost! It can no longer be reinforced by our forces.
{reinforce_region_FAILURE}You have failed to reinforce this region and left it vulnerable to attack, the Council hopes this is all part of some master strategy.
{reinforce_region_PROPOSAL}This region is the frontier to our enemies, but is undermanned and vulnerable to attack. The Council suggests you increase our forces here by at least 4 units.
{reinforce_region_SUCCESS}Well done, you have successfully reinforced this region against attacks from our foes, the Council is comforted by your wisdom.
{reinforce_region_TITLE}Reinforce Region
{return_papal_settlement_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Everchosen by failing to return his lands to chaos.
{return_papal_settlement_PROPOSAL}The Everchosen has requested that you return his lands to Undivided. His unHoliness will be greatly in your debt if you can see fit to return his home city.
{return_papal_settlement_SUCCESS}You have greatly pleased the Everchosen by successfully returning his lands to Undivided.
{return_papal_settlement_TITLE}Return the Everchosen's lands to Undivided.
{send_emissary_EXPIRY_DEATH}The faction you were to meet with has been vanquished. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to them.
{send_emissary_FAILURE}You have failed to establish diplomatic relations with these people, the Council hopes this is for the best.
{send_emissary_PROPOSAL}There are foreigners almost at our very gates and we know very little of them. The Council suggests you send an emissary to this faction and initiate diplomatic relations.
{send_emissary_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully established diplomatic relations with these people; the Council admires the ease with which you handle diplomacy.
{send_emissary_TITLE}Send Emissary
{steal_general_EXPIRY_GENERAL_DEATH}Alas this marriage can never be, the general has died, and nearly left our Princess a widow.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_DEATH}Alas, the poor Princess has died; we must call the marriage off.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_RETIRED}Our Princess is now too old to marry; her time would be better spent on more solitary and contemplative pursuits. The marriage is off.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_TARGET_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, and this lord is twice such, he has married another. The marriage to our Princess is off.
{steal_general_FAILURE}You have not arranged the marriage this Council recommended. The Council bows to your greater judgement in these matters.
{steal_general_FAILURE_PRINCESS_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, it seems our Princess has married another, the original marriage is off.
{steal_general_PROPOSAL}Lord %S has been beguiled by the lovely Princess %S. He is willing to pay a handsome dowry for her hand in marriage. The Council recommends you arrange this marriage as soon as possible.
{steal_general_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully arranged the marriage we recommended. This union is sure to bear fruit in time.
{steal_general_TITLE}A Proposal for the Princess's Hand
{teutonic_assassinate_general_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This character has become our ally, and killing him is not required.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_EXPIRY_DEATH}This character is dead, and killing him is not required.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_EXPIRY_HIDING}This character has hide himself, and killing him is not required.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_EXPIRY_RELIGION}This hero realized error of his beliefs and renounced paganism, killing him is not required.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_FAILURE}You did not remove this man. The Council will consider this failure as a part of your grand design...
{teutonic_assassinate_general_PROPOSAL}This man is a living abomination - a non-believer. He must be put to the sword.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_SUCCESS}You have been succesful. Your devotion to Sigmar is noted.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_TITLE}Murder pagan commander
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This character has become our ally. His removal has lost all meaning.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_EXPIRY_DEATH}This character is no longer dangerous to our people. There is no need to kill him.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_EXPIRY_HIDING}This character is nowhere to find. The quest for his head had ended.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_FAILURE}A simple man escaped you. How was that even possible?
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_PROPOSAL}This character is dangerous for our people - he tests our servants' faith. He must be dealt with.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_SUCCESS}You are commended gor your dealing with this man.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_TITLE}Murder the Priest
{teutonic_captureconvert_EXPIRY_ALLIED} These people became our allies. You don't have to capture their settlement.
{teutonic_captureconvert_EXPIRY_LOST}This settlement was captured by other people.
{teutonic_captureconvert_EXPIRY_RELIGION}The people of this power have realized how wrong their actions were, and they embarked on the path of truth. You don't need to capture this settlement.
{teutonic_captureconvert_FAILURE}You did not capture this settlement. Do you think you are better than the Everchosen himself?
{teutonic_captureconvert_PROPOSAL}Everchosen wants you to  capture this settlement and bring its inhabitants to his worshippers.
{teutonic_captureconvert_SUCCESS}The seeds of conversion bring their first fruit.
{teutonic_captureconvert_TITLE} capture and convert the settlement's residents to the true faith.
{teutonic_convert_FAILURE}How can you command a nation if you are unable to show the light of true faith in this small settlement?
{teutonic_convert_PROPOSAL} Now, this settlement is in your power. Hurry up to draw his people into the true faith! Sigmarists must be at least% d%% of the population.
{teutonic_convert_SUCCESS} His Holiness is happy - you are fulfilling his wishes.
{teutonic_convert_TITLE} Appeal to the true faith.
